Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 3: Boxes 45-52 1870-2017
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 3: Boxes 45-52
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 3: Boxes 45-52 1870-2017
5583/5
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives
49.4 linear ft.
Records (documents), publications (documents).
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Due to the volume of material in this collection the finding aid has been divided into three sections.
Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Section 3: Boxes 45-52
SUBJECTS
Names:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives.
Subjects:
Industrial relations -- United States -- Sources.
Form and Genre Terms:
Records (documents); Publications (documents)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Other sections of this Collection:
5583/5: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5
5583/5: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
5583/5: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Related Collections:
5880: Archives Organization File V, Additional Company Documents
5583/1: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1
5583/2: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
5583/3: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3
5583/4: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 4. Corporate and Organizational Publications
5583/6: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 6
5956: Archives Organization File Additional records
CONTAINER LIST
- Saturday Blade -- May 6, 1905 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Teamster Strike, Publication (Box 49, Folder 1)
    By The Saturday Blade. May 6, 1905. Item is in English.
- British Workman -- 1870, Publication (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The British Workman, 1870, Publication (Box 49, Folder 2)
    By British Workman Office. Item is in English.
- British Workman -- 1871, Publication (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The British Workman, 1871, Publication (Box 49, Folder 3)
- New York State and Local Employees' Retirement System, Publication (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: A Message from New York State Comptroller Hevessi, Publication (Box 50, Folder 1)
    By New York State and Local Employees' Retirement System. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: A Message from H. Carl McCall, Publication (Box 50, Folder 1)
    By New York State and Local Employees' Retirement System. Summer 2002. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Hold the Date! SRLC Annual Meeting, Publication (Box 50, Folder 1)
    By The South Central Regional Library Council Newsletter. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: A Message From Comptroller McCall, Publication (Box 50, Folder 1)
    By New York State and Local Employees' Retirement System. Spring 2002. Item is in English.
- New York State Workers Compensations Board, Publication (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Women and Workers' Compensation in New York State, Publication (Box 50, Folder 2)
    By New York State Workers' Compensation Board. April 1997. Item is in English.
- Public Services International, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Public Services International Constitution, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    By Public Services International. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: PSI Constitution, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Flash, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    By Public Services International. December 2004. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Flash, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    By Public Services International. October 2004. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Flash, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    By Public Services International. September 2004. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Flash, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    By Public Services International. August 2004. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Flash, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    By Public Services International. July 2004. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Flash, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    By Public Services International. February 2004. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Flash, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    By Public Services International. December 2003. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Flash, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    By Public Services International. January 2003. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Flash, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    By Public Services International. July 2003. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Flash, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    By Public Services International. August 2003. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Flash, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    By Public Services International. September 2003. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Flash, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    By Public Services International. November 2003. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Flash, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    By Public Services International. May 2003. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Flash, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    By Public Services International. 2002 March. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Flash, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    By Public Services International. July 2002. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Flash, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    By Public Services International. June 2002. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Flash, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    By Public Services International. December 1999. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Flash, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    By Public Services International. May 2000. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Flash, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    By Public Services International. September 2000. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Flash, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    By Public Services International. October 2000. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Flash, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    By Public Services International. May 2001. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Flash, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    By Public Services International. June 2001. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Flash, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    By Public Services International. August 2001. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Flash, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    By Public Services International. September 2001. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Flash, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    By Public Services International. February 2000. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Flash, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    By Public Services International. July 1999. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Report of Activities, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Rugmark Foundation, Publication (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Dear Friend, Publication (Box 50, Folder 4)
    By Pharis J. Harvey. June 2000, Postcard. Item is in English.
- Specialized Carriers and Rigging Assoc., Publication (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Exploring the Lattice-Boom Truck Crane Niche, Publication (Box 50, Folder 5)
    By Specialized Carriers and Rigging Association. January/Febraury 2001. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Multi-Modal Moves, Publication (Box 50, Folder 5)
    By Specialized Carriers and Rigging Association. March 2001. Item is in English.
- Strive: East Harlem Employment Service, Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: STRIVE's 2006 Gala Celebration, Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
    By Strive. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Strive's 2007 Gala Celebration, Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
    By Strive. Tuesday, November 6, 2007. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Letter to Mr. Kheel Center, Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: The Network Agenda The Israel Connection, Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Strive Raises $300,000 at First Benefit Gala, Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: 20th Anniversary Benefit Dinner, Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
    By Strive. March 4, 2004. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Dear Mr. Center:, Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
    By Strive. November 21, 2003. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Dear Friend of Strive, Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
    By Strive. July 18, 2003. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Strive Names National HQ The Harry and Jeanette Weinburg Center, Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
    By Strive. Spring/Summer 2003. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The ED Speaks Interns, Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
    By Strive. Fall/Winter 2002. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Strive Chicago Merge with Suburban Job-Link, Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
    By Strive. Fall/Winter 2003. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: National Summit Motivates Network, Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: STRIVE/ East Harlem Employment Service, Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
    By Strive. 7/23/2002. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: National Headquarters, Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: Dear Mr. Center, Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
    By Strive. November 4, 2004. Item is in English.
- Union Network International Statues, Publication (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Statutes and Congress Standing Orders, Publication (Box 50, Folder 7)
    By Union Network International. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Statutes and Congress Standing Orders, Publication (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Union Network International, 2000; Publication (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: First UNI World Executive Board Meeting: Edinburgh, 19-20 July 2000, Publication (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: New Rights for People in the New Economy, Publication (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Networked Solidarity: Multinationals and Workers' Capital, Publication (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Organising in the Network Economy, Publication (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: UNI and the New Economy, Publication (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Union Network International - 1st UNI World Congress, 2001; Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: 1st UNI World Congress: Consultation on Reports, Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Composition of the UNI World Executive Board, Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Letter to all UNI affiliates, Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
    By Philip Jennings. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Anthrax Kills two US postal workers, Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Global Action @ UNI for People in the New Economy, Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: 1st UNI World Women's Conference, Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
    By Union Network International. September 3-4, 2001. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Net.news, Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Code of Professional, Social & Ethical Responsibility for Professional and Managerial Staff, Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
    By FIET. Uni Commerce was formerly known as FIET. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: 1st World Congress, Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
    By Union Network International Resolutions. September 5-9, 2001. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Report on the 1st UNI World Congress, Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
    By Union Network International. September 5-9, 2001. Item is in English.
- Union Network International, 2001-2002; Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Working Abroad UNI Guidelines, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: ILO Welcomes UNI-Telefonica Pact, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Third Global Agreement Ready for Signing, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Labour Rights Infringed at European Central Bank, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Battle for Social Dimension Goes on After Doha, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: UNI Mission to Crisis-Hit Argentina, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
    By Union Network International. 1/29/2002. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Zimbabwe Struggles to Defend Trade Union Rights, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
    By Union Network International. March 21, 2002. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Solidarity & Campaigns Bulletin, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
    By Union Network International. March 21 2002. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Argentina Faces Humanitarian Crisis, UNI Warns, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: To all affiliated organisations, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
    By Union Network International. January 31 2002. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: International Justice for Janitors 2001, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
    By Union Network International. May 16, 2001. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: UNI opens doors-official, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: ICFTU Statement for Qatar Ministerial Conference, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
    By Philip Jennings. November 9-13, 2001. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The UNI Passport, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
    By Philip Jennings. February 13, 2001. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: UNI World Congress Statements, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
    By Union Network International. October 15, 2001. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Trade Union Guide on IMF Consultations, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Item 17: New General Secretary at the ICFTU, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
    By Union Network International. Novmber 26, 2001. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: UNI World Women's Committee Composition, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Item 19: Business Convergence and Concentration in the New Economy, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
    By Union Network International. July 19-20, 2000. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Composition of the UNI World Executive Board, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Union Labor Insurance Company, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Union Labor Life's J for Jobs Reports 168.05 Million in Mortgage Activity in First Quarter 2001, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    By Union Labor Life Insurance Co. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: ULLICO Inc. To Acquire Amalgamated Bank of Chicago in Move to Expand Financial Services to American Labor Market, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Unison, Publication (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Annual 2003/2004, Publication (Box 50, Folder 12)
    By Unison. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Annual Report 2003/2004, Publication (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Upstate History Alliance, Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: South Central DHP News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
    By Upstate History Alliance. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Professional Development and Training, Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
    By South Central Documentary Heritage Program. August-September 2003. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: South Central DHP News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
    By Upstate History Alliance. Summer 2002. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Professional Development and Training, Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
    By South Central Documentary Heritage Program. November-December 2003. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Word on Women, Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
    By Upstate History Alliance. Spring 2003. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: DHP Wins Archives Award, Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
    By Upstate History Alliance. Fall 2003. Item is in English.
- Urban Habitat Program, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Race, Poverty, and the Environment: A Journal for Social and Environmental Justice, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
    By Urban Habitat Program. Spring 2007. Item is in English.
- US Department of Labor, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Federal Minimum Wage, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    By US Department of Labor. Item is in English.
- Workers Rights Consortium (WRC), Publication (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: WRC Analysis of Severance Dispute at BJ&B, Publication (Box 50, Folder 16)
    By Workers Rights Consortium (WRC). Item is in English.
- Working Families Party (WFP), 2000-2005; Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: WFP Update: Why We Do What We Do, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Working Families Party. May 2005. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: WFP Update: The Battle is Joined, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. March 2005. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: WFP Update: Privatize This!, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. February 2, 2005. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: What a person is worth, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. April 1, 2004. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: WFP Update: Class, Race, Taxes and Drug Laws, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. December 21, 2004. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: WFP Update: Stuck in a Non-Swing State, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. October 26, 2004. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Two Weeks To Go, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. October 19, 2004. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Hypocrisy with a Capital H, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Working Families Party. August 27 2000. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: One Sweet Victory, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Working Families Party. September 23, 2004. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Overrides and Drug Laws, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. August 12, 2004. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Pataki Veto, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. July 30, 2004. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: One for Our Side, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. July 22, 2004. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Student Assistance Needed, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Richard Strassburg. July 22, 2004. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Minimum Wage Moment of Truth, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. June 7, 2004. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: It's Your Own Fault, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. January 27, 2004. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Astrology and the Minimum Wage, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. December 10, 2003. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: A Shift in the Landscape, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. November 11,2003. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Crunch Time, aka Election Day, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. November 2, 2003. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Vote NO on 'Non-Partisan' Question #3, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. October 30, 2003. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Brooklyn Judges/Big Potatoes and More, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. October 21, 2003. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Election Returns, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. September 11, 2003. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Working Families Party Update, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. September 8, 2003. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: WFP Members and Friends, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. April 25 2003. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: WFP Members and Supporters, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. August 2001. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Friends of the Working Families Party, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By The Executive Committee and Staff of the WFP. September 2001. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Albany: Good, Bad, and Ugly, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. July 26, 2003. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: WFP Members and Friends, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. February 2003. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: A Little Help From Our Friends, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. February 13, 2003. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: The War, Overseas and at Home, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. March 20, 2003. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: A Thanksgiving Sampler of Our wn, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. November 27, 2002. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Election Day Approacheth, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. November 4, 2002. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Live from New York, or, E is for Effort, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. November 6, 2002. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: WFP Members and Friends, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: WFP Members and Friends, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. April 2002. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: You Gotta Have HART (not to mention Carl, Liz, Steve, Lee, and Terry), Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. February 2002. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: A Special Election, A Special Woman, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. January 2002. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Minimum Wage, Maximum moment, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. June 2002. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Ashcroft, Rs and Ds, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. January 30, 2001. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: A Time to Act, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. May 2001. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: The Joint was Jumpin', Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Working Families Party. March 19, 2001. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: The Joint was Jumpin', Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. March 19, 2001. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Update #2, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. February 26, 2001. Item is in English.
  - Item 43: FAQ(Frequently Asked Questions), Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Working Families Party. Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Working Families Party Statement of Principles, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Item 45: Local Contacts, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Working Families Party. 4/3/00. Item is in English.
  - Item 46: 2000 Legislative Agenda, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Item 47: For Students, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Item 48: For Students, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Item 49: Working Families Structure, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Item 50: Affiliated Organizations, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Item 51: WFP History, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Item 52: A Living Wage for Working Families, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Item 53: WFP Shows Strength in Spring Elections, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Item 54: Executive Committee Statement on Patrick Dorismond Shooting WFP State Convention, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Working Families Party. March 26, 2000. Item is in English.
  - Item 55: Working Families Part Backs Hil's Senate Bid, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Working Families Party. March 27, 2000. Item is in English.
  - Item 56: Join Communit and Labor Activists for the First Annual Working Families Party State Convention, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Item 57: March Update, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. March 29, 2000. Item is in English.
  - Item 58: Summer Update, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. July 2001. Item is in English.
  - Item 59: Our Two Cents, and One Unbelievable Story, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. December 15, 2000. Item is in English.
  - Item 60: Dear brothers and sisters:, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Ray Rogers. October 2000. Item is in English.
  - Item 61: Dear brothers and sisters:, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Item 62: A Working Third Party, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Micah L. Sifry. November 6, 2000. Item is in English.
  - Item 63: Crunch Time, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Item 64: Dear Friends:, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. November 6, 2000. Item is in English.
  - Item 65: Making Choices, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. September 2001. Item is in English.
  - Item 66: Ross Perot and Michael Bloomberg, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    By Dan Cantor. November 2001. Item is in English.